<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Alexandria Tour Guide</string>

    <string name="about_fragment">About</string>
    <string name="hotels_fragment">Hotels</string>
    <string name="sights_fragment">SightSeeings</string>
    <string name="food_fragment">Food</string>

    <string name="city_name">Alexandria</string>

    <string name="about_city">
        Alexandria is a Mediterranean port city in Egypt.
        During the Hellenistic period,
        it was home to a lighthouse ranking among the Seven Wonders of the Ancient World
        as well as a storied library. Today the library is reincarnated in the disc-shaped,
        ultramodern Bibliotheca Alexandrina. The city also has Greco-Roman landmarks,
        old-world cafes and sandy beaches. Its 15th-century seafront Qaitbay Citadel is now a museum.
    </string>
    <string name="area">Area:</string>
    <string name="area_info"> 2,679 km²</string>
    <string name="weather">Weather:</string>
    <string name="weather_info"> 12°C, Wind SW at 8 km/h, 82% Humidity</string>
    <string name="postal_code">Postal code: </string>
    <string name="postal_code_info"> 21500</string>
    <string name="time_zone">Time Zone:</string>
    <string name="time_zone_info">GMT +2</string>
    <string name="population">Population</string>
    <string name="population_info">5.2 million (Oct 2018)</string>

    <string name="four_seasons">Four Seasons Hotel</string>
    <string name="four_seasons_detials">
        Set in an architectural landmark, Hotel San Stefano features a fashionable resort setting
        with a private sandy beach and overlooking the Mediterranean Sea.
    </string>

    <string name="tolip">Tolip Hotel </string>
    <string name="tolip_details">
        This 5-star hotel in Alexandria offers an outdoor pool, a spa and a gym.
        It features modern accommodation with views of the sea or city.
        Free Wi-Fi is available in public areas.
    </string>

    <string name="hilton">Hilton Alexandria Corniche</string>
    <string name="hilton_details">
        Boasting an ideal location in the heart of Alexandria, 
        Hilton Alexandria Corniche features its own private beach and wellness facility.
    </string>

    <string name="helnan">Helnan Palestine Hotel</string>
    <string name="helnan_detials">
        Set on 350 acres of lush gardens overlooking a Mediterranean cove,
        Helnan Palestine Hotel features an outdoor pool and private seafront sun terrace.
    </string>

    <string name="sheraton">Sheraton Montazah</string>
    <string name="sheraton_details">
        Sheraton Montazah features a well-equipped gym and free-form pool offering panoramic sea views.
        Located 10 minutes’ walk from El Mandara Railway Station, its rooms have a private balcony.
    </string>

    <string name="paradise">Paradise Inn Beach Resort</string>
    <string name="paradise_detials">
        Overlooking Mamoura beach, Paradise Inn Beach Resort offers rooms with a spa bath and a balcony.
        The hotel has a large pool and spacious gardens.
    </string>


    <string name="lighthouse">Lighthouse of Alexandria</string>
    <string name="lighthouse_details">The Lighthouse of Alexandria,
        sometimes called the Pharos of Alexandria, was a lighthouse built by the Ptolemaic Kingdom, 
        during the reign of Ptolemy II Philadelphus, 
        which has been estimated to be 100 metres in overall height.
        \nDestruction date: 1480
        \nConstruction started: 280 BC
        \nLocation: Pharos, Alexandria, Egypt
        \nDestroyed by: Earthquake
        \nArchitect: Sostratus of Cnidus
        
    </string>

    <string name="bibliotheca">Bibliotheca Alexandrina</string>
    <string name="bibliotheca_details">
        The Great Library of Alexandria in Alexandria, Egypt,
        was one of the largest and most significant libraries of the ancient world.
        The Library was part of a larger research institution called the Mouseion,
        which was dedicated to the Muses, the nine goddesses of the arts

        Address: Al Azaritah WA Ash Shatebi, Qesm Bab Sharqi, Alexandria Governorate 21526
        Hours Open : 10AM–7PM
        Phone: 03 4839999
    </string>

    <string name="citadel">Citadel of Qaitbay</string>
    <string name="citadel_details">
        The Citadel of Qaitbay is a 15th-century defensive fortress located on the Mediterranean sea
        coast,in Alexandria, Egypt. It was established in 1477 AD by
        Sultan Al-Ashraf Sayf al-Din Qa\'it Bay.
        The Citadel is situated on the eastern side of the northern tip of Pharos Island
        at the mouth of the Eastern Harbour.

        Address: As Sayalah Sharq, Qesm Al Gomrok, Alexandria Governorate
        Hours Open: 8AM–5PM
    </string>

    <string name="montaza">Montaza Palace</string>
    <string name="montaza_details">
        Montaza Palace is a palace, museum and extensive gardens in the Montaza district of
        Alexandria, Egypt. It was built on a low plateau east of central Alexandria overlooking a
        beach on the Mediterranean Sea.

        Address: Al Mandarah Bahri, Qism El-Montaza, Alexandria Governorate
        Hours Open: 8AM–12AM
    </string>

    <string name="pillar">Pompey\'s Pillar</string>
    <string name="pillar_detials">
        Pompey\'s Pillar is a Roman triumphal column in Alexandria, Egypt,
        the largest of its type constructed outside the imperial capitals of Rome and Constantinople,
        located at the Serapeum of Alexandria

        Address: Pompey\'s Pillar, Al Karah WA at Toubageyah WA Kafr Al Ghates, Qesm Karmouz,
        Alexandria Governorate
        Hours Open: 9AM-3PM
    </string>

    <string name="royal_jewlry">Royal Jewelry Museum</string>
    <string name="roayl_jewlry_details">
        The Royal Jewelry Museum is an art and history museum in the Zizenia neighborhood of
        Alexandria, Egypt. It is located in the former palace of Princess Fatma Al-Zahra\'.
        The building\'s halls contain an inestimable collection of jewels and jewelry of the
        Muhammad Ali Dynasty

        Address: Pasha, 27 Ahmed Yehia, San Stifano, Qism El-Raml, Alexandria Governorate
        Hours Open: 9AM–4PM
    </string>


    <string name="foul">ALEXANDRIAN BREAKFAST FOUL</string>
    <string name="foul_detials">
        Eating Egyptian breakfast is one of the most memorable things you can do in Egypt,
        and this Egyptian Breakfast is no exception, it will blow your mind!
        The Foul Fava bean dip comes with tahini and a light tomato cilantro salsa,
        and the felafel is shaped into round balls! When you sit down, t
        he waiter brings you a table full of delicious side dishes to dip your baladi bread into as well!
    </string>
    <string name="eat_it_here_foul">
        MOHAMED AHMED RESTAURANT
        \nMust Order: Alexandrian Foul, Felafel, Fried cheese, signature scrambled eggs
        \nAddress: Qesm Al Attarin, Alexandria Governorate, Egypt
        \nPrice: 50 EGP + for 2
    </string>

    <string name="fonde">DELICIOUS ALEXANDRIAN FONDUE</string>
    <string name="fonde_details">
        Coming to Egypt I never thought there would be a famous fondue dish,
        but here in Alexandria it is a must try! Their secret 7 cheese mixture is amazingly
        fragrant and you can order it with a huge variety of different meats or seafoods.
        I ordered the beef with caramelized onions and pepper along with the shrimp and crab
        sticks with cheese. Amazingly creamy and cheesy!

        You can take your Vino bread sticks; a very soft almost baguette like bread,
        break it and make it into a long spoon, and scoop up your delicious Egyptian fondue!
    </string>
    <string name="eat_it_here_fonde">
        ALBAN SEWISRA
        /nMust Order: The beef with onions is called "lahma bel basal" and the shrimp and crab sticks
        is "fwakeh el bahr". You can also say seafood as it will be understood in English!
        \nComments: There may be a long lineup!
        \nAddress: Al Ibrahimeyah Bahri WA Sidi Gaber, Qesm Bab Sharqi, Alexandria Governorate
        \nPrice: 60+ EGP for two
        \nHours: Always busy, best to come earlier, but you can also come late at night too!
    </string>

    <string name="sea_food">DELICIOUS EGYPTIAN SEAFOOD!</string>
    <string name="sea_food_details">This was honestly some of the best seafood I ever tried.
        Located in a busy seafood market of Alexandria,
        the best part is how you can purchase all of your seafood fresh right in the market
        and bring it literally 5 meters to the side to one of the busy seafood grills.
        You only pay their cooking fee, which was modest, 80 EPG, around $4 USD.
        My favourite dish was the squid with tomato, onion, chili,
        and cilantro. It was amazingly fragrant and slightly sweet from the onion,
        with a slight spicy kick from the chili!
        All of the Egyptian seafood is cooked here in many different ways,
        allowing you to try many different flavours, so make sure to buy a lot of seafood from the market!
        Get some crab, fish, and squid!
    </string>
    <string name="eat_it_here_sea_food">
        SEAFOOD JOINT AT SOUQ EL MIDAN, BAHARY
        \nMust Order: It is prepared many different ways. Try to eat one of each different style; baked, grilled, sauteed.
        \nComments: Best dish was the squid!
        \nAddress: Ash Shamarli WA Zaweyat Al Aarag, Qesm Al Gomrok, Alexandria Governorate
        \nPrice: Pay their cooking fee, usually around 2$ to 5$.
        \nHours: Come early because the fresh seafood in the market is in the morning. Ideally come before 12 oclock.
    </string>

    <string name="liver">EGYPTIAN LIVER SANDWICHES</string>
    <string name="liver_details">
        Although this is just one dish, there are actually many dishes that come with it!
        While the liver sandwiches weren’t my favourite, the selection of side dishes and the pure
        variety of flavours alone is worth coming here for! As with most Egyptian restaurants,
        there\’s delicious humous, tahini, baba ganoush, and vegetable dishes.
    </string>
    <string name="eat_it_here_liver">
        EL-SAYED MOHAMMED KARIM
        \nMust Order: Liver sandwiches, brain sandwich, stuffed intestine with fragrant rice
        \nAddress: As Sayalah Sharq, Qesm Al Gomrok, 28 Alexandria Governorate
        \nHours: Come in the evening
    </string>

</resources>
